easyuni.com 2015-03-23

# Privacy Statement - Study abroad or locally - EASYUNI

This Privacy Statement ("Privacy Policy") describes EASYUNI's policies and procedures on the collection, use and disclosure of your information when you use the EASYUNI's website. We will not use or share your information with anyone except as described in this Privacy Policy. This Privacy Policy does not apply to information we collect by other means (including offline) or from other sources. Capitalized terms that are not defined in this Privacy Policy have the meaning given them in our Terms and Conditions. By accessing or using the website, you agree to this Privacy Policy.

## Information We Collect and Use

EASYUNI uses information we collect to operate, maintain and provide you the features and functionality of the website, to analyze how the website is used, diagnose website or technical problems, maintain security, personalize content, remember information to help you efficiently access your account, monitor aggregate metrics such as total number of visitors, traffic, and demographic patterns, and track Content and users as necessary to comply with the Digital Millennium Copyright Act and other applicable laws.

**Information You Provide** : You provide us information about yourself, such as your name and e-mail address, if you register for an account with the website, including by connecting with the website via a third-party website, or by “following,” “becoming a fan,” adding the EASYUNI application, etc., on a third party website or network. Your name, email address and other information you choose to provide on the website will be forwarded to the University, College or their representatives when you submit an application for University or College admissions via our website.

We may use your email address to send you website-related notices (including any notices required by law, in lieu of communication by postal mail). We may also use your contact information to send you marketing messages. If you don’t want to receive these messages, you can opt out by following the instructions in the message. If you correspond with us by email, we may retain the content of your email messages, your email address and our responses.

If you choose to use our invitation website to invite a friend to the website, we will ask you for that person’s email address and automatically send an email invitation. EASYUNI stores this information to send this email, to register your friend if your invitation is accepted, and to track the success of our invitation website.

**Content** : You also provide us information in Content you post to the website. Your Content (such as reviews, photos and videos) and metadata about your Content will be viewed by other users. EASYUNI can, but has no obligation, to monitor your Content you post on the website. We can remove any information you post for any reason or no reason.

**Cookies** : When you use the website, we may send one or more “cookies” – a small data file – to your computer to uniquely identify your browser and let EASYUNI help you log in faster and enhance your navigation through the site. A cookie may convey anonymous information about how you browse the website to us. A persistent cookie remains on your hard drive after you close your browser so that it can be used by your browser on subsequent visits to the website. Persistent cookies can be removed by following your web browser’s directions. A session cookie is temporary and disappears after you close your browser. You can reset your web browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, some features of the website may not function properly if the ability to accept cookies is disabled.

**Log Files** : When you use the website, our servers automatically record certain information sent by your web browser. These server logs may include information such as your web request, Internet Protocol (“IP”) address, browser type, referring / exit pages and URLs, number of clicks and how you interact with links on the website, domain names, landing pages, pages viewed, mobile carrier, and other such information.

**Clear Gifs Information** : When you use the website, we may employ clear gifs (also known as web beacons) which are used to track the online usage patterns. In addition, we may also use clear gifs in HTML-based emails sent to our users to track which emails are opened by recipients. The information is used to enable more accurate reporting and make EASYUNI better for our users.

**Geo-Location Information** : When you use the website by or through a mobile device, we may access, collect, monitor and/or remotely store “location data,” which may include GPS coordinates (e.g. latitude and/or longitude) or similar information regarding the location of your mobile device. Location data may convey information about how you browse the website to us. Location data does not collect or share any personally identifiable information about you. Location data may be used in conjunction with personally identifiable information. Some features of the website, particularly location-based websites, may not function properly if use or availability of location data is impaired or disabled.

**Device Identifiers** : When you access the website by or through a mobile device, we may access, collect, monitor and/or remotely store one or more “device identifiers.” Device identifiers are small data files or similar data structures stored on or associated with your mobile device, which uniquely identify your mobile device and are used to enhance the website. A device identifier may be data stored in connection with the device hardware, data stored in connection with the device’s operating system or other software, or data sent to the device by us. A device identifier may convey information about how you use the website to us. A device identifier does not collect or share any personally identifiable information about you. A device identifier may be used in conjunction with personally identifiable information. A device identifier may remain persistently on your device, to help you log in faster and enhance your navigation through the website. Some features of the website may not function properly if use or availability of device identifiers are impaired or disabled. EASYUNI may access, collect and/or store device identifiers upon enabling EASYUNI’s websites.

**Third Party Tools** : EASYUNI uses third party analytics tools, such as Google Analytics, to help understand use of the website. Many of these tools collect the information sent by your browser as part of a web page request, including cookies and your IP address. These analytics tools also receive this information and their use of it is governed by their privacy policy.

## How We Share Your Information

**Your Use** : We will forward your Personal Information as part of the application form to the University or College or their official representatives when you make the application for admission on the website.

**Service Providers, Business Partners, and Others** : EASYUNI may share your personally identifiable information with other third parties for the purpose of providing the website to you. If we do this, such third parties’ use of your information will be bound by this Privacy Policy. We may also store personal information in locations outside the direct control of EASYUNI (for instance, on servers or databases co-located with hosting providers).

**Business Transfers** : As we develop our business, we may buy or sell assets or business offerings. Customers, email, and visitor information is generally one of the transferred business assets in these types of transactions. We may also transfer or assign such information in the course of corporate divestitures, mergers, or dissolution.

**Third Party websites** : We may share your information with a third party application with your consent, for example when you choose to access our websites through such an application. We are not responsible for what those parties do with your information, so you should make sure you trust the application and that it has a privacy policy acceptable to you.

**Compliance with Laws and Law Enforcement Requests; Protection of EASYUNI's Rights** : EASYUNI may disclose your personal information if required to do so by law or subpoena or if we believe that it is reasonably necessary to comply with a law, regulation or legal request; to protect the safety of any person; to address fraud, security or technical issues; or to protect EASYUNI’s rights or property.

**Non-Personally Identifiable Information** : We may disclose your non-private, aggregated, or otherwise non-personally identifiable information, such as anonymous usage data, platform types, etc., with interested third parties to help them understand the usage patterns for certain EASYUNI websites.

## How We Protect Your Information

The security of your information is important to us. In the event that personal information is compromised as a result of a breach of security, EASYUNI will promptly notify those persons whose personal information has been compromised, in accordance with the notification procedures set forth in this Privacy Policy, or as otherwise required by applicable law.

## Your Choices About Your Information

You may, of course, decline to submit personally identifiable information through the website, in which case EASYUNI may not be able to provide certain services to you. You may update or correct your account information at any time by logging in to your account. You can delete your EASYUNI account by visiting our Account Deletion page.

## Children’s Privacy

Protecting the privacy of young children is especially important. Our website is not directed to persons under 13. EASYUNI does not knowingly collect or solicit personal information from anyone under the age of 13 or knowingly allow such persons to register with the website. If we become aware that we have collected personal information from a child under age 13 without verification of parental consent, we take steps to remove that information. If you believe that we might have any information from or about a child under 13, please contact us at privacy@easyuni.com.

## Links to Other Web Sites

We are not responsible for the practices employed by websites linked to or from our website, nor the information or content contained therein. Please remember that when you use a link to go from our website to another website, our Privacy Policy is no longer in effect. Your browsing and interaction on any other website, including those that have a link on our website, is subject to that website’s own rules and policies.

## Changes to Our Privacy Policy

If we change our Privacy Policy, we will post those changes on this page to keep you aware of what information we collect, how we use it and under what circumstances we may disclose it. Changes to this Privacy Policy are effective when they are posted on this page. This policy was last modified on Feb 9, 2012.

## Contact Us

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact us at privacy@easyuni.com.
